(Sheldon:)Wow, this is hard.
They got me a motorized dirt bike.
(Penny:)No.
What 12-year-old boy
wants a motorized dirt bike?
(Penny:)All of them.
- Really?
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Huh.
(Penny:)- So we're getting this one?
- Yeah, I suppose.
All right, let's go.
(Random woman:)Excuse me,
do you know anything about this stuff?
(Sheldon:)I know everything about this stuff.
(Woman:)Okay, I have my own
wholesale flower business.
I wanna hook up my computer
in the front...
(Woman:)...with the one
in my refrigerated warehouse.
Buy this one, it's the one we're getting.
Happy guy.
(Sheldon:)No, she doesn't want that.
She needs a point-to-point peer network
with a range extender.
- Thank you.
- Which hard drive do I want?
(Random guy:)- FireWire or USB?
- It depends on what bus you have available.
(Guy:)I drive a Chevy Cavalier.